<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to LiberCarta on LiberCarta</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to LiberCarta on LiberCarta</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 21:18:54 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sipho Moloi</title><link>/authors/sipho-moloi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/authors/sipho-moloi/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sipho Moloi is an independent author based in Ottawa, Ontario. In 2015, his short story Front received an Honourable Mention in the Ottawa Public Library&amp;rsquo;s Awesome Authors contest. He has been writing since a young age, with a focus on science fiction and military fiction.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>His work is influenced by a variety of sources, including video games, films, and literature. Sipho&amp;rsquo;s storytelling is driven by a core principle: it must be engaging. His writing is known for dynamic action, well-developed characters, and compelling narratives.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About LiberCarta</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 21:18:54 -0700</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>LiberCarta&lt;/strong> is a home for independent voices and the stories they dare to tell.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We celebrate the richness of independently crafted books. These may come from self-published authors, small publishing houses, or unconventional creative efforts. This is a place where writers don&amp;rsquo;t wait for permission to be read. Here, authors own their narratives, and readers discover stories beyond the expected.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="why-we-exist">Why We Exist&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In a world flooded with algorithms, bestseller lists, and mainstream publishing gates, indie authors often go unseen. Yet their stories are brave, bold, and beautifully different. We created LiberCarta to change that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>Have a question? Want to say hello?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Libercarta is a small, growing project and we would love to hear from you. Whether you are an author, reader, or supporter, feel free to reach out.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Use the form below to get in touch. We will do our best to reply soon.&lt;/p>


&lt;iframe data-tally-src="https://tally.so/embed/wQXEkl?alignLeft=1&amp;hideTitle=1&amp;transparentBackground=1&amp;dynamicHeight=1" loading="lazy" width="100%" height="324" frameborder="0" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0" title="Contact form
">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;script>var d=document,w="https://tally.so/widgets/embed.js",v=function(){"undefined"!=typeof Tally?Tally.loadEmbeds():d.querySelectorAll("iframe[data-tally-src]:not([src])").forEach((function(e){e.src=e.dataset.tallySrc}))};if("undefined"!=typeof Tally)v();else if(d.querySelector('script[src="'+w+'"]')==null){var s=d.createElement("script");s.src=w,s.onload=v,s.onerror=v,d.body.appendChild(s);}&lt;/script></description></item><item><title>Join The Authors</title><link>/get-involved/join-the-authors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/get-involved/join-the-authors/</guid><description>&lt;p>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to get to know you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please share a few details about yourself so we can create your author page on LiberCarta. This includes your name, a short bio, and optionally a headshot or links to your website or social profiles.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Your email will not be published. We&amp;rsquo;ll only use it to contact you if needed.&lt;/p>


&lt;iframe data-tally-src="https://tally.so/embed/nrpqYp?alignLeft=1&amp;hideTitle=1&amp;transparentBackground=1&amp;dynamicHeight=1" loading="lazy" width="100%" height="528" frameborder="0" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0" title="Author Form">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;script>var d=document,w="https://tally.so/widgets/embed.js",v=function(){"undefined"!=typeof Tally?Tally.loadEmbeds():d.querySelectorAll("iframe[data-tally-src]:not([src])").forEach((function(e){e.src=e.dataset.tallySrc}))};if("undefined"!=typeof Tally)v();else if(d.querySelector('script[src="'+w+'"]')==null){var s=d.createElement("script");s.src=w,s.onload=v,s.onerror=v,d.body.appendChild(s);}&lt;/script></description></item><item><title>Submit Your Book</title><link>/get-involved/submit-your-book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/get-involved/submit-your-book/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ready to have your book featured on LiberCarta?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Use the form below to share your book details, including the title, description, genre, and cover image. If you have already submitted your author information, this will help us connect your book with your author page.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You are welcome to submit more than one book. Please fill out a separate form for each title.
We will not share your email address and will only contact you if we need to clarify anything.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>